In this video,
how quickly could I give you 40 lessons
that could save
you the years that I wasted so
that you could accomplish more than what
I've
accomplished in a shorter period of time
and eat less shit?
First of all, why should you listen to me?
Because I have one of these. No.
You can get one of them from having a few
viral reels. Don't be impressed by those.
But do make sure if you have one,
that it's in the background.
Rule number one, no one cares about you.
And I know this can sound really horrible
and morbid to begin with, but think about
this.
Everyone just cares about themselves.
It's such a beautiful thing
that you can understand and learn,
and it will save you
so much time, not just on YouTube,
but every single social media platform.
People are just out for themselves.
And you think, what about people that
are generous, that give to charity?
Philanthropic.
They're doing it because it makes them
feel better.
Even when I buy dinner for my friends,
they think I'm being kind. I'm not.
I do not enjoy people buying dinner for
me. It makes me feel uncomfortable.
I did not do it because I like you people.
I did it because it makes me feel better.
So when creating a video,
especially the packaging,
but especially what you talk
about in the video,
it must do something for other people.
So even if you want to talk about yourself
and the weight that you lost, the muscle
you built,
even the way you communicate has to be
changed.
So if you did want to lose those five
pounds of excess weight,
I would suggest that
you do these things because they worked
for me.
And it's imperative
that you stay on top of your progressive
overload so you can
get the results.
If you just talk about yourself in
content, people leave.